http://www.bchs.edu/terms-and-conditions

Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions | Baptist Health Sciences University
Library
About UsAccreditationMission Vision & ValuesFaculty & Staff DirectoryInterprofessional EducationWhat's Happening at BaptistStudent Consumer InformationAcademicsBiomedical SciencesDiagnostic Medical SonographyHealth AdministrationMedical Imaging SciencesMedical Laboratory ScienceMedical RadiographyNeurodiagnostic TechnologyNuclear Medicine TechnologyNursingPopulation HealthPre-Health StudiesRadiation TherapyRespiratory CareGeneral EducationAdmissionsAdmission to the CollegeVisit CampusVirtual TourImportant Deadlines(TTP) Tennessee Transfer PathwaysTransfer Credit InformationArticulation AgreementsCitizenship/Residency RequirementCourse DescriptionsHonors ProgramCredit for Prior LearningDual EnrollmentSummer EnrollmentTuition & Financial AidTuition & FeesRefund of Tuition & FeesTuition and Fee EstimatorOther CostsPolicies1098-Tax InformationDirect DepositApplying for AidAid EligibilityApplying for a LoanFormsScholarships & GrantsFederal/State Financial AidSenior Year Tuition Deferral ProgramGraduate StudentsFinancial LiteracyFinancial Aid Code of ConductNet Price CalculatorCampus LifeOffice of Faith and ServiceCampus HousingCampus Safety & SecurityCenter for Academic ExcellenceStudent EventsStudent OrganizationsStudent PoliciesStudent ServicesCOVID-19
Breadcrumb
Home
Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions
Baptist Health Sciences University Website Privacy Policy and Terms And Conditions of Use
Introductory Information. Baptist University’s website is provided to you (hereinafter “You”, “Your” or “Yourself”) under the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of Use (hereinafter “Agreement”)by Baptist Health Sciences University (hereinafter “Baptist University”, “We”, “Our” or “Us”). Baptist University has issued this Agreement to help define Our expectations regarding Your use of Our web site (hereinafter “Site”) as well as describe Our commitments to You. We reserve the right to replace, supplement, revise or otherwise amend this Agreement at any time and for any reason without prior notice to You by posting a revised Agreement to Our Site. Your use of Our Site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Agreement and Your continued usage after a revised Agreement is posted constitutes acceptance of the revised Agreement. We will maintain a copy of the most current Agreement on Our Site. Any revised Agreement is effective immediately upon being posted on Our Site and it is Your responsibility to periodically review and familiarize Yourself with the most current Agreement.
1.1. Our Site contains information, data, software, photographs, graphics, videos, text, images, typefaces, sounds and other material (collectively “Content”) that may be protected by copyrights, trademarks, or other proprietary rights. The Content may consist of copyrighted works proprietary to Us or to third parties who have provided Us with Content.
1.2. You may use the Content only for Your own, non-commercial, private, educational use, provided You do not delete or change any copyright, trademark or other proprietary notices and that the Content is not altered in any way.
1.3. You may not sell, reproduce, distribute, modify, display, prepare derivative works based on, report or otherwise use any Content in any way for any public or commercial purpose. None of the Content may be reverse-engineered, disassembled, decompiled, transcribed, reproduced, translated into any language or computer language, retransmitted in any form or by any means, resold or redistributed without Our prior written consent. Any unauthorized or unapproved use of any of the Content may constitute copyright infringement and may subject You to civil and criminal liability provided for under domestic and international copyright laws and treaties.
1.4. Baptist University, its associated logos, and other marks clearly identified in the site as Baptist University’s are Our trademarks. All other names, brands and marks are used for identification purposes only and may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. Any reproduction, distribution, public performance, or public display of these materials, in whole or in part, is prohibited without Our express prior written permission.
1.5. For Your convenience, We may provide links on Our Site to third party web sites which will allow You to leave Our Site. These third party web sites are not under Our control and We are not responsible for any such third party web sites or the content provided therein, or for any link contained in a linked site, or for any changes to or updates to such sites. Unless expressly stated by Us, We do not recommend or endorse particular products, services or web sites of any third parties or make any determination whether any such product, service, or web site may be either necessary or appropriate for any use.
1.6. To facilitate Your access to and use of Our Site or portions thereof, We may make certain software available to you. The terms of Your use of such software will be stated separately in a license agreement that will be included with the software. You agree to only use such software in a manner permitted pursuant to such license agreements.
Web Site Privacy Policy. We have implemented this Web Site Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate Our firm commitment to Your privacy and the privacy of Your information. This Web Site Privacy Policy is supplemental, but not superior, to any state or federal law, rule, regulation or regulatory advisory opinion. We recognize that the security of Your information is of great concern and We try to protect Your privacy in several ways, some of which are as follows:
2.1. We use Secure Socket Levels (SSL), encryption, digital certificates, and/or other equivalent technology to ensure a secure connection from Your Web browser or application to Our Site.
2.2. We require reliable verification of Your identity (authentication) by requiring both a user ID and a password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of Your user ID and Your password and/or any other account information. YOU MUST NEVER REVEAL EITHER YOUR USER ID OR YOUR PASSWORD TO ANY OTHER PERSON FOR ANY REASON. Baptist University reserves the right to cancel Your user ID and/or password upon learning that it has been revealed to any person other than You.
2.3. No third party site is subject to this Web Site Privacy Policy. Therefore, if You choose to link to a third party site from Our Site, You should review the privacy policies of each site You visit. We are not responsible for any disclosures You make on any third party sites or any security breaches emanating from any third party site.
2.4. Cookies are small computer files that We transfer to Your computer’s hard drive. These files help Us determine which features and services are being utilized and the activities that You perform while visiting Our Site. Our cookies may or may not be automatically deleted once You leave Our Site.
2.5. We collect information about You through the enrollment process, Our Site and through other avenues. Additional information may be collected through Your voluntary participation in surveys, questionnaires, etc. When possible, Your information is maintained on a secure server with limited access by Baptist University personnel. Baptist University may also store the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of the computers You use to visit Our Site.
2.6. The way that We may use Your information includes, but is not necessarily limited to, the following:
2.6.1. To enable Us to process and verify enrollment and conduct security activities;
2.6.2. To contact You regarding enrollment or enrollment-related matters;
2.6.3. To notify You concerning changes to Baptist University, Our Site or this Agreement;
2.6.4. To perform research about Our Site’s content and services for the purpose of additional development and improvement;
2.6.5. To aggregate data to help improve Baptist University and Our Site’s content and services;
2.6.6. To offer services on a limited basis to demographically identified groups of students;
2.6.7. To direct editorial content to students most likely to be interested in the specific subject matter;
2.6.8. To advise students of new Site features; and
2.6.9. In any other reasonable manner.
2.7. Except as identified in this Agreement, We do not routinely provide or release Your name or e-mail address to any third party without Your prior permission. However, We may disclose Your information to third parties if required to comply with applicable legal requirements such as a search warrant, subpoena, court order, law or other regulation. We may also disclose Your information in case of a physical threat to You or in any other special or unique circumstance.
2.8. If necessary to provide products and services related to the maintenance of Our Site, We may provide Your information to Our vendors. We will attempt to require that each of these vendors not further use or disclose Your information for any purpose other than providing Us or You with products and services, but no such guarantee or warranty is made by Us.
2.9. Notwithstanding the foregoing, You acknowledge and agree that We are only required to use reasonable precautions to maintain the security and privacy of Your information and that We make no guarantee or warranty that We shall successfully maintain the security and privacy of Your information.
Terms of Service.
3.1. You agree to comply with all laws directly or indirectly applicable to the gathering, use, transmission, processing, receipt, reporting, disclosure, maintenance, and storage of electronic information, and to cause all persons or entities under Your direction or control to comply with such laws. You agree to use reasonable efforts to maintain the confidentiality of such information and prevent the disclosure of such information to third parties except as permitted by law.
3.2. You acknowledge and agree that the information contained on Our Site is not necessarily considered complete or accurate and that We provide this information “as is” without warranty of any kind. We do not warrant against interruptions, losses, delays, human or machine errors, omission, including loss of data. You agree that We shall have no liability for any of the information provided through Our Site or through any links to sites external to Our Site. You agree that We shall have no liability for actual, special, incidental or consequential damage of any kind or nature that may cause a loss of data or use of Our Site. Additionally, You agree that We shall have no liability to any third party resulting from this Agreement or the services provided hereunder.
3.3. Upon any breach of this Agreement, including inappropriate or unauthorized use or other misuse of Your right to access Our Site, We shall have the right to immediately terminate Your access to Our Site without notice to You.
3.4. This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between You and Us and supersedes all prior agreements and understandings, whether written or oral, relating to the subject matter of this Agreement.
3.5. This Agreement shall be construed, interpreted, and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee without reference to the principles of conflict of laws.
3.6. We may assign Our rights under this Agreement at any time to an affiliate of Baptist University or Baptist Memorial Health Care Corporation without Your prior consent, provided such assignment is in conformance with state and federal law governing the electronic transfer of student information. You will not assign, sublet, or further subcontract any of Your rights and/or duties under this Agreement without Our prior written consent.
3.7. If any provision of this Agreement shall be held to be invalid, illegal or otherwise unenforceable, the validity, and enforceability of the remaining provisions shall in no way be affected or impaired thereby.
3.8. Our or Your failure at any time to require performance by the other of any provision of this Agreement shall in no way be taken or held to be a waiver of any further breach of the same provision or any other provision.
3.9. This Agreement shall be construed in favor of a meaning that permits Us to comply with FERPA and the regulations promulgated pursuant thereto.
God's Blessings
For the Lords gives wisdom; from His mouth comes knowledge and understanding
Proverbs 2:6
Tweets by @BCHSMemphis
Doctor of Nurse Practitioner Program graduates its first students
On August 13, Baptist College of Health Sciences held a walk-thru graduation and private event for our Doctor of Nursing Practice graduates.
Read
Baptist Health Sciences University
Baptist Health Sciences University
1003 Monroe Ave.,
© 2020 by Baptist Health Sciences University. All rights reserved.
